we need to
select both fish and lizard from pets
at the same time and assign that return
value to a variable named my pets
then we will print the value of my pets
as part of a sentence
we know that we can use array element
reference to
select a particular element from an
array
in this problem we want to select both
fish
and lizard
so let's select fish by referencing the
array element at index 2
and also select lizard which is at index
3.
now we'll run our code
and you can see that we successfully
selected both
fish and lizard
however the problem description tells us
that we need to select both
fish and lizard at the same time
when using array element reference we're
not
limited to passing in only a single
index
we can also pass in a range
in this case we want to select the
elements of the array
from index 2 through 3.
placing a range within these square
brackets will return an
array with the elements at the indexes
included in this range
if we had a larger array
we could pass in the range from 2 to 5
and the elements at index 2 3
4 and 5 would be returned in this new
array
so that we can see that this does return
an array
let's output the return value with p
you can see the returned array includes
our desired elements
now according to our problem description
we need to assign this returned array
to a variable mypeds
now we need to output both elements of
this
my pets array as part of a sentence
because my pets is an array we will
again need to use
element reference to interpolate the
correct
element of the my pets array first we
want to select
fish the first element of our my pets
array
and we can do that by referencing the
element at index
0 the first element
to access the second element of our
array
lizard
we will reference the element at index
1.
let's run our code and see if we've
gotten the expected output
and we have
you